When we think of low temperature as a danger, we often imagine people working outside in polar regions in the depths of winter or in cold storage facilities, layered in thermal clothing to help them deal with freezing temperatures.
当我们将低温视作一种危险时，往往会想到隆冬时节在极地户外工作、或是在冷藏设施里作业的人，他们裹着一层层保暖衣物来抵御严寒。
But do we also need to protect ourselves when it's just a bit chilly as well as in arctic conditions?
但除了极寒环境，当天气只是有点微凉时，我们也需要做好自我防护吗？
As mammals, our bodies have to maintain an internal temperature in a narrow range between 37 and 37.5C.
作为哺乳动物，我们的身体必须将核心体温维持在37至37.5摄氏度的狭窄区间内。
If that temperature drops, the effects can be serious.
一旦体温下降，就可能引发严重后果。
Below 35C, people can develop hypothermia, with symptoms such as shivering, confusion, and slurred speech.
体温低于35摄氏度时，人会患上低温症，出现颤抖、意识模糊、言语不清等症状。
If body temperature drops below 29C, it can lead to loss of consciousness.
若体温降至29摄氏度以下，可能会导致意识丧失。
Fortunately our bodies can regulate their internal temperature, but there are some negative side effects which come with this process.
幸运的是，我们的身体能够调节核心体温，但这个过程也会带来一些负面的副作用。
Ten degrees Celsius is hardly biting cold, but that's the temperature that BBC journalist James Gallagher was made to endure in an experiment at the University of South Wales.
10摄氏度算不上刺骨严寒，但这正是BBC记者詹姆斯·加拉格尔在南威尔士大学的一项实验中所要承受的温度。
As the test room was cooled from 21 degrees, his blood pressure, heart rate and breathing rate all increased, while the flow of blood to his brain decreased by 20%.
随着实验室的温度从21摄氏度逐渐降低，他的血压、心率和呼吸频率全都有所上升，而流向大脑的血流量则减少了20%。
What are the consequences of this?
这会带来什么后果？
Immediately, it meant that Gallagher took longer to solve some simple puzzles.
最直接的影响是，加拉格尔解开一些简单谜题的时间变长了。
As a longer-term risk, Professor Damian Bailey points out that increased blood pressure puts us at greater risk of stroke and heart attacks.
达米安·贝利教授指出，长期来看，血压升高会让我们面临更高的中风和心脏病发作风险。
Professor Bailey suggests that in the cold, people should wear clothing that provides good insulation, eat more carbohydrates, and be more active.
贝利教授建议，在寒冷环境中，人们应该穿着保暖性好的衣物，摄入更多碳水化合物，同时增加活动量。
Another approach is suggested by Professor Christopher Minson.
克里斯托弗·明森教授则提出了另一种方法。
He believes that people are too reliant on being able to control the temperature around them, and that we can gradually train ourselves to cope with a lack of warmth and be comfortable at lower temperatures.
他认为，人们过于依赖控制周围环境的温度，而我们可以逐步训练自己适应不那么温暖的环境，在更低的温度下也能感到舒适。
So, while moderately low temperatures can have an effect on us, there are steps we can take to cope with them.
所以，即便一般程度的低温会对我们产生影响，我们依然可以采取一些措施来应对。